(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,o,t){},14:function(e,o,t){"use strict";t.r(o);var s=t(2),n=t(3),r=t(7),i=t(5),a=t(0),c=t.n(a),_=t(4),u=t.n(_),l=(t(13),[{question:"A light sensitive device that converts drawing, printed text or other images into digital form is______   ",answers:["Keyboard","Plotter","Scanner","OMR"],correct:"Scanner",questionId:"099099"},{question:"Which protocol provides e-mail facility among different hosts______",answers:["FTP","SMTP","TELNET","None of these"],correct:"SMTP",questionId:"183452"},{question:"The basic architecture of computer was developed by_____",answers:["John Von Neumann","Charles Babbage","Blaise Pascal","None of these"],correct:"John Von Neumann",questionId:"267908"},{question:"In how many generations a computer can be classified______",answers:["3","4","5","6"],correct:"5",questionId:"333247"},{question:"Fifth generation computers are based on_______",answers:["Artificial Intelligence","Programming Intelligence","VVLSI","None of these"],correct:"Artificial Intelligence",questionId:"496293"},{question:"Microprocessor was introduced in which generation of computer_______",answers:["Second Generation","Fourth Generation","Both (A) and (B)","Third Generation"],correct:"Fourth Generation",questionId:"588909"},{question:"Which of the following memory is non-volatile______",answers:["SRAM","DRAM","ROM","All of the above"],correct:"ROM",questionId:"648452"},{question:"GUI stands for______",answers:["Graph Use Interface","Graphical Universal Interface","Graphical User Interface","Graphical Unique Interface"],correct:"Graphical User Interface",questionId:"786649"},{question:"Any data or instruction entered into the memory of a computer is considered as________",answers:["Storage","Output","Input","Information"],correct:"Input",questionId:"839754"},{question:"Which one of the following is not an application software package______",answers:["Red Hat Linux","Microsoft Office","Adobe Pagemaker","Open Office"],correct:"Red Hat Linux",questionId:"98390"},{question:"Which of the following statement is wrong_______",answers:["Photoshop is a graphical design tool by Adobe","Linux is free and open source software","Linux is owned and sold by Microsoft","Windows XP is an operating system"],correct:"Linux is owned and sold by Microsoft",questionId:"1071006"},{question:"An error is also known as______",answers:["Bug","Debug","Cursor","Icon"],correct:"Bug",questionId:"1174154"},{question:"Microsoft Word is an example of_______",answers:["an operating system","Processing device","Application software","an input device"],correct:"Application software",questionId:"1226535"},{question:"Who invented the supercomputer_______",answers:["Charles Babbage"," JH Van Tassell","Charles Ginsberg","Seymour Cray"],correct:"Seymour Cray",questionId:"1310938"},{question:"Graphical pictures that represent an object like file, folder etc are_______",answers:["Task bar","Windows","Icons","Desktop"],correct:"Icons",questionId:"1436873"},{question:"The 0 and 1 in the binary numbering system are called Binary Digits or_______",answers:["Bytes","Kilobytes","Decimal bytes","Bits"],correct:"Bits",questionId:"1515110"},{question:"The IC chip used in computers, is made of________",answers:["Chomium","Iron Oxide","Silica","Silicon"],correct:"Silicon",questionId:"1642728"},{question:"Which of the following operating systems is produced by IBM_______ ",answers:["OS-2","Windows","DOS","UNIX"],correct:"OS-2",questionId:"1747256"},{question:"The processor which performs arithmetical and logical operations is called______",answers:["Control","ALU","Register","Cache Memory"],correct:"ALU",questionId:"1822532"},{question:"Which was an early mainframe computer_______",answers:["UNIC","FUNTRIA","BRAINIA","ENIAC"],correct:"ENIAC",questionId:"195075"},{question:"Which of the following was the first Intel processor introduced_______",answers:["3080","4004","8080","8086"],correct:"4004",questionId:"2019778"},{question:"Which network protocol is used to send Email_______",answers:["FTP","SSH","POP3","SMTP"],correct:"SMTP",questionId:"2134343"},{question:"When was the first e-mail sent_______",answers:["1963","1969","1971","1974"],correct:"1971",questionId:"2210799"},{question:"Operating System is the most common type of _________ software.",answers:["Communication","Application","System","Word Processing Software"],correct:"System",questionId:"2379831"},{question:"RAM chips________",answers:["Licorice","Lollipop","Chocolate","Bubblegum"],correct:"Licorice",questionId:"2426418"},{question:"The operating system manages________",answers:["Memory","Processor","Disk and I/O Devices","All of the above"],correct:"All of the above",questionId:"2510086"},{question:"Which memory is non volatile and may be written only once_________",answers:["RAM","EEPROM","EPROM","PROM"],correct:"PROM",questionId:"2685745"},{question:"The memory which is programmed at the time it is manufactured is________",answers:["RAM","ROM","PROM","EPROM"],correct:"ROM",questionId:"2796884"},{question:"Which of the following memory is volatile_____",answers:["RAM","ROM","EPROM","PROM"],correct:"RAM",questionId:"2838900"},{question:"A kilobyte also referred to as KB, is equal to_____",answers:["1000 bytes","1024 bytes","2048 bytes","512 bytes"],correct:"1024 bytes",questionId:"298060"},{question:"Which of the following items is not used in Local Area Networks (LANs)_______",answers:["Computers","Modem","Printer","Cable"],correct:"Modem",questionId:"3096579"},{question:"Computer Virus is a _______",answers:["Hardware","Software","Bacteria","Freeware"],correct:"Software",questionId:"3182461"},{question:"The most advanced form of ROM is______",answers:["PROM","RAM","EEPROM","Cache Memory"],correct:"EEPROM",questionId:"3239112"},{question:"Another term for Main Memory is______",answers:["Hard Disk","ROM","Floppy Disk","RAM"],correct:"RAM",questionId:"3318503"},{question:"One MB is equal to_______",answers:["1024 Byte","1024 KB","1000 KB","1024 GB"],correct:"1024 KB",questionId:"3410327"},{question:"Internet Explorer is a type of______",answers:["Operating System","Browser","IP address","Compiler"],correct:"Browser",questionId:"3542596"},{question:"AVI format was developed by________",answers:["IBM","Apple","Microsoft","Macromedia"],correct:"Microsoft",questionId:"3667517"},{question:"______ is the high speed memory used in the computer.",answers:["RAM","Hard Disk","Cache","BIOS"],correct:"Cache",questionId:"3791672"},{question:"A collection of 8 bits is called______",answers:["Byte","Record","Word","Nibble"],correct:"Byte",questionId:"3893585"},{question:"The term memory applies to which one of the following",answers:["Logic","Storage","Input Device","Output Device"],correct:"Storage",questionId:"3913430"},{question:"The device primarily used to provide hardcopy is the______",answers:["CRT","Computer Console","Printer","Card Reader"],correct:"Printer",questionId:"4049121"},{question:"Which of the following is the most powerful type of the computer________",answers:["Mainframe","Super conductor","Micro computer","Super computer"],correct:"Super computer",questionId:"4150746"},{question:"A list of instructions used by a computer is called______",answers:["Text","CPU","Program","Output"],correct:"Program",questionId:"4235063"},{question:"The process of copying data from a memory location is called______",answers:["Writing","Controlling","Booting","Reading"],correct:"Reading",questionId:"4321002"},{question:"The process of putting data into a storage location is called_____",answers:["Reading","Writing","Controlling","Hand Shaking"],correct:"Writing",questionId:"4442286"},{question:"You should save your computer from______",answers:["Viruses","Time bombs","Worms","All of the above"],correct:"All of the above",questionId:"4564430"},{question:"Which of the following is program group______",answers:["Accessories","Paint","Word","All of above"],correct:"Accessories",questionId:"4630606"},{question:"Which is not application software_______",answers:["Windows NT","Page Maker","WinWord XP","Photoshop"],correct:"Windows NT",questionId:"4795960"},{question:"The ________ program compresses large files into a smaller file",answers:["WinZip","WinShrink","WinStyle","None of above"],correct:"WinZip",questionId:"4811162"},{question:"Which of the following is an example of a real time operating system______",answers:["Lynx","MS DOS","Windows XP","Process Control"],correct:"Arby's",questionId:"4982981"}]),d=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(l.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},h=t(6),m=function(e){var o=e.question,t=e.options,s=e.selected,n=Object(a.useState)(t),r=Object(h.a)(n,2),i=r[0],_=r[1];return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionBox"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},o),i.map((function(e,o){return c.a.createElement("button",{key:o,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){_([e]),s(e)}},e)})))},p=function(e){var o=e.score,t=e.playAgain;return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},"Your Scored ",o," / 5 correct answer!"),c.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:t}," ","Play again!"))},f=function(e){Object(r.a)(t,e);var o=Object(i.a)(t);function t(){var e;Object(s.a)(this,t);for(var n=arguments.length,r=new Array(n),i=0;i<n;i++)r[i]=arguments[i];return(e=o.call.apply(o,[this].concat(r))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0},e.getQuestions=function(){d().then((function(o){e.setState({questionBank:o})}))},e.computeAnswer=function(o,t){o===t&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<5?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.playAgain=function(){e.getQuestions(),e.setState({score:0,responses:0})},e}return Object(n.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"title"},"Quiz - Test Your Computer Skills"),this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(o){var t=o.question,s=o.answers,n=o.correct,r=o.questionId;return c.a.createElement(m,{question:t,options:s,key:r,selected:function(o){return e.computeAnswer(o,n)}})})),5===this.state.responses?c.a.createElement(p,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain}):null)}}]),t}(a.Component);u.a.render(c.a.createElement(f,null),document.getElementById("root"))},8:function(e,o,t){e.exports=t(14)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e13c6c8c.chunk.js.map